so I'm gonna read you something I get
some I get a lot of mail and I don't
know where I got this I've been a lot of
different places in the last week and
this showed up at one of them and I'm
going to read it to you I have no idea
what to make of it it's written in a
female hand so that's about all I can
tell but there's no address or name on
it this isn't a question but a comment
or more accurately perhaps a message I
spent this past weekend in an ayahuasca
ceremony which for those of you who
don't know is a South American visionary
plant medicine some of you may roll your
eyes at this but ayahuasca brings you
into direct contact with the archetypal
realm of being users of this medicine
initiates I should say refer to
ayahuasca as she because the spirit of
the plant is decidedly feminine and
encounter with ayahuasca is an encounter
with the great mother of creation the
goddess the void from which all things
come the feminine counterpart of logos
dr. Peterson you appeared in one of my
ayahuasca visions
might account for why I've been rather
fatigued lately dr. Peterson you
appeared in one of my ayahuasca visions
and I asked asked her who is Jordan
Peterson what is he doing which is
something I'd really like to know as
well and she responded with crystalline
clarity quote here he is here to invoke
and initiate the divine masculine
principle on earth at this time so I'm
up here to thank you deeply and
profoundly on behalf of the great mother
herself the goddess the Divine Feminine
principle who has been eagerly awaiting
the awakening of the masculine principle
into divinity and service so you know
get a letter like that every day
actually I get a letter to like that
every day